indiavideo.org 2009-08-08

# Privacy Policy

**Website :** The term website refers to the site www.keralavideos.com, collectively, including all content available through the domain name www.keralavideos.com

**Third Party Website :** The term third party website refers to all or any website owned and or controlled by any individual, corporate body or any type of entity other than Invis Multimedia Pvt. Ltd. 

**User :** The term ‘user’ refers to any person who visits the Website www.keralavideos.com or access the content of the Website www.keralavideos.com by any mode of form and also include contributors as referred to in para. 

**User Information :** The term user information refers to any information voluntarily submitted by the user as well as any other information collected by the Company while using the site or collected as pre-condition for using the site. It includes both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information. 

**Company :** The term ‘company’ refers to Invis Multimedia Private Limited a company registered under the Companies Act of India which owns and controls the Websites www.keralavideos.com, www.invis.in and other sites. 

**Privacy Notice**

The Company recognizes that the users of the Website value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details information on the use and disclosure of user information collected by the Company. The user can make an informed decision regarding whether to use or continue using the Website.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use of the Website. The user’s use of the Website and any personal information the user provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and Terms of Use of the Website.

Personal information submitted by the user to the Website is being used to operate, maintain, and provide the features and functionality of the Website. 

Any personal information or text, videos, graphics, photos, sound, music, and the like content that the user voluntarily discloses online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. The user’s account name is displayed to other Users when the user upload videos or send messages in the Website and other Users can contact the user through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the Website may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

Email address or other personally identifiable information will not be used to send commercial or marketing messages without the user’s consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which the user will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. The Company may, however, use the user’s email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes of the Website or of the Company. 

The Company may provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to its subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on its behalf. However the Company will use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

The Company may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with laws of the Republic of India.   

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

The Company allows other companies, to serve advertisements within the Website. These institutions may use technology to send, directly to the user’s browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website and they may receive the user’s IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

The user should consult the respective privacy policies of these advertising companies for more information on their practices. The Website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and the Website or company cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Special Note to International Users**

The Website is owned by the Company and the Company is registered under the laws of the Republic of India and the Company is situated within India. only the Indian laws are applicable for any sort of use, transaction or interaction with the Website. 

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy**

In the event that the Company or the Website is acquired by or purchased by or merged with a third party entity, the Company reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information the Company have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of the Company’s bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, the Company may not be able to control how the user’s personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

**Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice**

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically. Please revisit this page every time to stay aware of any changes. The user’s continued use of the Website constitutes the user’s agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

**Date Last Modified:**  
This Privacy Notice was last modified 24/05/2007 

**Jurisdiction :**  
User accepts that any matter arising in relation to the privacy policy of the Website will be decided within the jurisdiction of Thiruvananthapuram Court.
